(A New Meeting)
- Nice to see you all. - Nice to see you.
Last week's preview went viral.
- Even I got so excited for it. - Right.
Team Chunk of our show got together.
Wait, you mean us?
- Team Chunk? - I saw that in a comment.
- Did you just call us Team Chunk? - You're the Chunk Trio.
I mean, it's fine for us.
- You can't call her that. - Right.
Just like HYORISOO,
- I'll be the third member... - Yes.
- The third member? - if I have to do it anyway.
- I'm the heaviest. - He's the heaviest.
- Second. Third. - Second. Third.
He's definitely the leader.
Right, he should be the leader.
To me, they all look like they could be their own leader.
- What do you mean? - Hey.
- How dare you say that to her? - I'll be the lightest member.
- I'm the lightest member. - How could you?
- The heaviest and the lightest. - I'm the lightest.
- The heaviest and the lightest. - The heaviest and the lightest.
- It will be a delicious segment. - Definitely.
I want our viewers to eat something before watching our episode.
- Is that really necessary? - They might get gastric acid.
- Gastric acid? - Something like that.
- Yes. - That's why I had triangle gimbap.
(That's why I had triangle gimbap.)
(How to Eat and Live Well)
It's the heaviest member.
Our dear heaviest member.
I'm a regular at this butcher shop.
My gosh. It's my first time watching you work.
The thing I asked for yesterday...
- arrived today. - Yes.
Why are you wearing a matching outfit to the meat?
- Hey. - It could've caused...
a huge misunderstanding.
- You almost got butchered. - Seriously.
I'm pork, and that's beef!
(Don't confuse the two!)
Seriously.
- He got a chuck flap tail pattern. - Right.
- He must be chuck flap tail. - I really want to grill you.
(Come on, what kind of joke is that?)
I bet it's really good grilled.
It was delivered fresh from Eumseong.
When did you get this meat then?
We bought it at an auction yesterday.
- Just yesterday? - It was processed then.
(It's fresh from yesterday's auction.)
- Really? - Yes.
It's got the freshest color.
(It's got the freshest color.)
(Salivating)
Does your mouth water just by looking at that?
- Let me explain. - People rarely salivate...
- when they see raw meat. - Listen.
What are you talking about? Check out that color.
- Of course. - Once you grill it...
Only lions drool when they see raw meat like that.
- Hey, you! - I'm so sorry.
- You're one of us. - Hey, be careful.
- I'll be careful. - You have to be careful.
(I'll be careful.)
(Carefully watching him butcher it while drooling)
The color definitely looks different.
My brother.
(My brother)
- Hey, Seon Min. - My brother.
- Gosh, you came right away. - I did.
Gosh, what's this?
- Hello. - You know who he is, right?
- "My brother." - It's Min.
The best comedian, Min, came.
We all went to a summer retreat a while ago.
He kept giving me the look.
At that moment, I sensed that...
he and I would get along well like good brothers.
(The two of them met as the same team, "Between Power and Ham.")
(As they joined hands and worked together,)
(their team won the game.)
We bonded...
- when we were on the same team. - Totally.
- We bonded deeply. - Yes.
It's Chobok.
To celebrate Chobok,
I invited close friends of mine to my place.
So I was there to get some high-quality ingredients.
I invited them because it was Chobok.
- To have invigorating food? - Yes.
- Seeing you in my neighborhood... - Yes.
- makes me so happy. - I'm happy to be here too.
- Let me explain. - On my way here...
I'm the honorary ambassador of Gangdong-gu.
- For real? - Yes.
I asked him to prepare this cut of meat a few days in advance.
It's my favorite cut.
(I set this up, so I could feed you the good-quality meat.)
(Amazed)
I can't wait to try it.
Do you want to try it raw to refresh your palate?
Sounds good.
You don't get that kind of service...
- unless you're a real regular. - Right.
- Just with some salt? - Wait.
- You're in Gangdong-gu. - Yes.
- You try it first. - My gosh.
- Try that. - Thank you.
(He dips it in salt...)
(and eats it in one bite.)
Isn't it good?
- Isn't it good? - It's super fresh.
Okay. Great.
Gosh, it's the freshest meat ever.
(Feeling proud)
What's going on?
You should try it too.
- You know what? - Come on.
- No. - I'm fine.
- You should try it too. - No.
- Sung Hwan. - I'll have it grilled later.
- No. You must try it. - Gosh, no.
Here's the thing. I love it too.
I have a very weak stomach. I must dip it in some sauce.
Sung Hwan.
- I didn't think you were that weak. - Seon Min.
No. I have a weak stomach.
I like staying at hotels. I don't like going camping.
That's where I lean toward.
Sung Hwan does have a weak stomach.
I see. You can't even eat raw beef?
You have to understand that I have a weak stomach...
despite how I look.
- It was freshly butchered. - I thought you were a cool guy.
- I thought you were a cool guy. - Look at his eyes.
You ought to try it.
(Grabbing)
My gosh. This looks good.
(Yes, I'm a cool guy.)
Isn't it good?
(Isn't it good?)
(Humming)
Yes, it was tasty.
I didn't know you were a picky eater.
- He's very picky about food. - It's...
- Right? - It's nice.
Come on, lighten up.
(Teary-eyed)
- Thank you. - Gosh, sir.
You have the freshest meat.
Gosh, the meat is so fresh today.
(He purchases the freshly butchered meat.)
I feel rich.
It's 410 dollars.
- What? - What?
My people were coming over. I had to treat them to a nice meal.
- Hwan is super cool. - Are you sure about this?
Come on. I'm the honorary ambassador of Gangdong-gu!
Is that a paying position?
No.
- It's an honorary position. - I'm just an honorary ambassador.
It's an honorary position.
(The honorary ambassador buys meat for his good friend.)
- Bye. - Thank you.
- Okay. - Bye.
- I won't see you off. - Okay.
- Shouldn't he be saying that? - That's...
That's my thing.
- "I won't see you off." - That's my signature line.
- Since we're in Gangdong-gu, - Yes.
I'll show you around.
- Gosh, this feels different. - It does, right?
- Welcome to Gangdong. - Oh, my.
This place is huge.
It's different, right?
I love this market.
Smell that.
(Invigorating dishes are everywhere as it's Chobok.)
That looks delicious.
(The market has seasonal seafood...)
(as well as seasonal fruits.)
All right. We need to buy a few things.
(Let's buy some groceries while we look around.)
I got hwachae. Then I need tofu, green onion kimchi...
- Are you opening a Korean buffet? - Gosh, no.
- Hold on. We need to... - Gosh, I love this market.
- What do we need to buy? - Hello.
- I'll get green onion kimchi. - Gosh.
- That's... - Right from the market.
- Nice. - How much?
Thank you. Put it in the basket.
- This looks authentic. - Their tofu is so good.
- Is it handmade tofu? - Yes, it is.
- Thank you. - Let me carry this.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
- Thank you. - Sell a lot.
Thank you.
How nice.
(Min and Hwan fill up the grocery bag.)
I love it.
- Let's get some brunch. - Yes.
My favorite snack bar is here.
- Snack food? That sounds good. - Yes. Let's eat something simple.
- We can't eat a lot here because... - Something simple?
we're going to get about three appetizers.
Three appetizers?
We're getting three appetizers.
That's the one.
- This is the place? - No, the one in front.
I love this place.
- A long time ago... - When I came back from Kazakhstan,
- that was the first place I hit up. - I see.
- After coming back to Korea? - With Ju Seung?
Yes, I went there with Ju Seung.
- My stomach is shrinking. - Oh, this episode?
(He went with Ju Seung.)
(The regular snack bar of the Gangdong-gu honorary ambassador)
- Sir, I'm here. - Hello.
- I'm here too. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - He's visiting Gangdong-gu today.
He bragged so much about this place. He said your food was amazing.
I'm the honorary ambassador of Gangdong-gu.
(Bowing)
- This is our appetizer spot. - Okay.
One fried squid, one gimmari,
- and one fried pepper. - Fried squid?
- I want you to try this tteokbokki. - Okay.
Once you try it, you see how thick and gooey this is.
- I love this kind of tteokbokki. - Let's put it down.
- It's rice-based tteokbokki. - It is.
That's the authentic tteokbokki.
It's tastier...
- when the sauce is thick like that. - Of course.
You try it first.
- Me? - Go ahead.
He's a guest in my town. He must try it first.
He always looks after Seon Min...
- first. - Right.
It's no joke, right?
(Hugging)
Gosh, this is so good.
It's the perfect level of spiciness for me.
- Right. - It's nice and spicy.
- It's thick, spicy, - Gosh, that looks good.
- and chewy. - It's super thick.
Rice-based tteokbokki must be nice and thick.
The rice cakes have to get stuck on your front teeth.
- That's exactly it. - It has to be a sticky bite.
- You're spot on. - Right.
- Finish the last piece. - Can I have that luxury?
Go ahead.
(Scraping)
- There you go. That hits the spot. - Gosh. Hey, you...
- Gosh. Hey, you... - This is it.
You know how to enjoy food.
- I had to finish the sauce too. - Exactly. You must eat it up.
(He scrapes the sauce and eats it up.)
- I'll share a useful tip. - Tell us.
They cover the plate with the plastic bag.
Grab the plastic bag and squeeze out the sauce.
- Then it ends up in a triangle. - Like a piping bag.
Treat it like a piping bag.
Tear it open with your nail and squeeze out the sauce.
- Like a freezie? - Yes.
It's really good...
- It was so good. - when you squeeze out the sauce.
(Make sure to eat every drop of the sauce.)
Gosh, we're off to a great start.
Goodness, it was good.
It was perfect.
- Let me pay for this. - Come on.
Don't.
I hate it when my people do that.
- Come on. - No!
- Sung Hwan. - I'm sorry. Don't make me yell.
Gosh, you're...
I can't allow that.
Sung Hwan.
He doesn't let his juniors spend money in Gangdong-gu.
Sung Hwan. Thank you for the food.
How much is it?
It's seven dollars.
- It didn't even cost that much. - Hey.
- Hold on. - I thought it was 70 dollars.
- I wanted to pay... - That's...
- because it was only seven dollars. - No, listen.
You're making a big deal out of it.
He made it sound like the meal cost 700 dollars.
Exactly.
- "No!" - Listen.
- This is so embarrassing. - My face is getting red.
- But you were still cool. - Really?
That's really cheap.
(He pays 7 dollars like a cool guy.)
It was so good.
I enjoyed your food once again.
Thank you.
I saw him and his parents on TV.
Out of all the comedians,
his popularity among people in their 20s and 30s is...
- He's the best. - the best.
(Smiling)
The young worker knows Seon Min.
It feels good when you bring a junior...
- It's a different feeling. - and they recognize you.
Right.
- We'll get going. - An autograph? Sure.
- Make it look cool. - Gosh, Seon Min.
(Here you go.)
This is a charming piece of paper.
- Here in Gangdong-gu... - Right on the take-out paper.
- No. Here in my town... - The take-out paper...
- It's like that here. Hey. - Look.
- That's the way to go at markets. - How charming.
It's the signature paper.
- I actually liked that. - You did. Right? Yes.
- When would you get this chance? - They'll frame it later.
(Adding Sung Hwan's name)
"With Ku Sung Hwan."
(Gosh, Min...)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- I'll come back. - See you next time.
(They fill up their stomach in a good mood.)
- Do you like sikhye? - Yes, I do.
Drinking sikhye washes down heavy, dense food.
- Really? - Of course.
Does sikhye help with digestion?
- Of course. It's got rice grains. - Not at all.
- No? - Come on. "Not at all?"
It helps digest food.
Why do you think I drink Coke Zero?
He's forcing the food to go down.
- It just feels like that? - He's washing it down.
(I like sikhye.)
- Hello. - Sir, we'll take sikhye.
- Sikhye? - Yes.
"Digestive medicine."
That's natural digestive medicine. I'm serious.
- It's natural digestive medicine. - It's my first time hearing it.
No. I'm serious.
My gosh. Thank you, sir.
- I'll carry this. - Thank you.
- Okay. - Okay. Have a good day.
Can I get an autograph?
An autograph? Sure.
- Gosh, another one. - On my phone, please.
On your phone?
Gosh, on his phone?
- Goodness. I... - After starring on our show...
People loved Seon Min.
- That's crazy. - You can't throw it out.
- Seon Min, you're super popular. - Right.
I was very grateful.
- That's... - Ho Young?
- How old are you? - I'm 23.
Yes. People in their 20s...
- love Seon Min. - Unbalanced arms.
My gosh. Thank you so much.
(He hands over the autographed phone.)
Thank you. One more?
- Yes. - Do you sell phones here?
My gosh, Seon Min.
He must have multiple phones.
The lady in the back wanted it too.
It's impossible for Seon Min to walk around.
At that moment, I remembered seeing him...
in the Buzz outfit.
- That was a critical moment. - Yes.
- Seriously. - That was his career crisis.
When CODE KUNST said Andy was there,
I had some doubt about him.
I vividly remember the look on Sung Hwan's face.
(Gazing)
The look on his face.
- What's that? - Sung Hwan!
- No! - I didn't see that.
No.
After seeing him at the market today...
(He had some doubt about Min after the talent show.)
I was quite surprised...
because the younger generation recognized him.
I saw how popular he was at the market today.
(He saw Min's class at the market.)
He's impressive.
- It was crazy. - Getting recognized at markets...
- makes you feel you're popular now. - Right.
People went crazy at the market. Seriously. To people in their 20s,
- he's like Seo Taiji. - Seriously.
(To people in their 20s, he's like Seo Taiji.)
My gosh.
- Seon Min. - Seo Taiji to people in their 20s?
- They don't know who he is. - They don't.
- People in their 20s... - Is he that obscure?
No.
- Be careful. - No one knows him.
People in their 20s don't know who Seo Taiji is.
That means Seon Min is not popular.
- That's true. - Really? Why?
- Back in my day, he was the bomb. - Listen.
- You're not in your 20s now. - That was when we were in our 20s.
- That was when we were in our 20s. - He's as famous as H.O.T...
when we were in our 20s.
- Seon Min is trending these days. - Exactly.
- He's super popular. - He's the most popular comedian.
- He's the most popular now. - I was so surprised.
(Min's popularity is a sensation.)
- Jang Mi. Thank you. - Thank you.
- Sell a lot. Thank you. - Have a good day.
(He finally leaves the stall.)
- Gosh, I love traditional markets. - Aren't they great?
- Yes. - They're nice, right?
- They recognized me. - How great is that?
- Let's go. - Did we buy everything?
- We got everything. - Let's go.
Let's go.
To the left. What a charming market.
What a lively market.
Seon Min, you were super popular at the market.
I was so surprised. I mean it.
(They arrive at Hwan's place in no time.)
- Gosh. - Thank you.
Welcome to my house.
Gosh, this is nice.
All right. Okay. Thank you.
(Giving Hwan the groceries)
Okay.
- What's that? Gosh. - What is that?
- The Bulgarian bag. - Why did you bring that?
(He puts the Bulgarian bag around his neck with some struggle.)
Okay.
Sung Hwan.
- All the way to the fifth floor? - Let's go.
(Do you think you can walk up to the 5th floor with that?)
The thing is, there's no elevator in my building.
- There's no elevator. - Neither does my building.
My gosh.
- Gosh, it's a 15kg bag. - Walking up is a good workout too.
I worked out my legs when I walked up the stairs.
My gosh.
(He arrives on the 5th floor while working out his lower body.)
This place looks hip.
(Panting)
My gosh.
- Welcome. - Sung Hwan.
Oh, my. Thank you.
Goodness, your house looks clean.
(Exhausted)
- Put it over there. - Your house looks amazing.
- Over there. - Okay.
My gosh.
By the way, why did you bring a Bulgarian bag?
All right. There.
This is for your workout.
It's a housewarming present.
What kind of lunatic gives a Bulgarian bag as a present?
- Me. I gave one to Ju Seung. - My gosh.
- Sung Hwan, it's still a present. - I'm that lunatic.
- I gave one to Ju Seung. - Yes.
- You did. - What's this?
(Moomoo gave it to Ju Seung as well.)
(A Bulgarian bag)
Is that also 15kg?
- Yes. - What's this?
I gave it a lot of thought, though.
I knew for sure that we would eat a lot that day.
- I bought that, - Right.
so it could help us digest.
This will help you make a lot of money this year.
- Sunflowers. - That's a good present.
I have one too.
People don't know, but Sung Hwan is particular about interior design.
I see. This is nice.
- Look at him. He's unhappy. - This is nice.
- He wears his heart on his sleeve. - Look at his mouth.
You know what? I really appreciate your thoughtfulness.
- Sung Hwan, I've got one more. - Hey!
(I've got one more.)
- What is that? - Earlier...
- I knew you were toying with me. - His reaction is different.
- It's a handkerchief. - Really? Gosh, that's crazy.
You mentioned a handkerchief earlier.
It's a three-handkerchief set.
(Hwan always carries this with him.)
- It's an essential item for him. - Being confident...
You're so sweet.
- Thank you. - He used it that morning too.
- You have the freshest meat. - That's nice. How thoughtful.
I was happy when I saw you use a handkerchief.
I love it. Hey, thank you.
- You sweat a lot. - I sweat so much.
- Use it well. Do you like it? - I love it.
I brought it today.
- It's the one he gave me. - I see.
Really?
- You're thoughtful. - Seriously.
- You're Soo Jong among comedians. - How thoughtful.
- Choi Soo Jong? - Choi Soo Jong.
Let's go to the rooftop.
I always wanted to visit.
So many people are curious about my rooftop.
My gosh. What an honor, Sung Hwan.
Seon Min is the first one to visit Sung Hwan's house.
- He's the first one. - Exactly.
- I was the first one? - Among the members of the show.
- This is fun. - Isn't it fun?
This side... Give me a second.
Sung Hwan.
- Sung Hwan. - This is no joke, right?
How did you do all this?
- Do what? - Did you paint everything?
How beautiful. You set it up...
- like a tourist spot. - Seriously.
- It's super impressive in person. - I mean...
- It was jaw-dropping. - It was so colorful.
- Seriously. It was beautiful. - It had good energy.
The color...
Yes. I wanted it to be pink.
It's so vibrant.
- You're like Paris Hilton. - Do you eat out here?
You love pink.
- My gosh. - Why...
Pink is perfect for men.
I love pink.
Looking at it now, it's totally giving raw-meat vibes.
- Hey, no. - What? Is it ox blood?
- He's in the offal shade. - Hey.
Come on. My rooftop looks beautiful. Why do you keep...
- Or chuck flap tail. - You're driving me crazy.
- Can I rent your rooftop sometime? - Sure.
- I'll let you use my rooftop. - Gosh.
Doesn't this place look better in person?
I love it here. It's brightening the atmosphere.
The atmosphere is different now.
Wait. You have a workout corner. Over there.
My gosh.
This is my workout zone.
- This is all you have? - Yes.
- I only work out on this. - That was all he had.
- Just this? - I can do everything with it.
(One's will is more important than any equipment.)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
- It's Fedor Workout from Russia. - Nice.
- Two. - Fedor Workout.
(From mastering Fedor Workout...)
(to dominating the park in Hong Kong)
My gosh. Look at his muscles.
(The global expert of bodyweight exercises, Hwan)
Sung Hwan is so strong.
You and I are alike.
(And he set foot in Hwan's zone.)
He's got a great posture.
(The ruler of workout areas on mountains, Min)
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
- You guys are similar. - Yes.
- You have the same hobby. - We vibe well together.
It looks like the three of us are different, but we all click.
- Yes. - No. I don't like to exercise.
- But you were a former judo player. - Right.
Gosh, I'm sick of it.
I won't do it again.
This is my favorite jersey.
- Are you sure I can put this on? - Of course.
I don't let anyone wear this.
(The two of them put on workout clothes.)
- They worked out first. - They did.
- On a summer day like this? - They were going to eat a lot.
- It looks like Sung Hwan's jersey. - It's mine.
- We were both going to sweat. - My gosh.
Right. It was nice.
You look different with the jersey on.
It's great, isn't it?
(We look pretty cool.)
- So... - What's your English name?
- My English name? - Yes.
- Should we name each other? - I already have one.
- What's yours? - It's Marcus.
- Marcus? That's a manly name. - Marcus. Yes.
Buzz.
- At least here today, - Yes.
- Marcus. Buzz. Okay. - you're Buzz.
- Wait, Buzz. - Okay, Marcus.
My gosh. What's this?
Oh, my.
- Gym gloves? - Gym gloves.
You came all the way to Gangdong-gu...
- from Yangcheon-gu. - Yes.
- Let's do a simple workout. - A simple workout.
- Let's loosen up our shoulders. - Okay.
(I'll teach you how we work out here in Gangdong-gu.)
My gosh, your arms...
Extend your arms like this.
- I have short arms. - I'm...
Phelps of Korea.
- Phelps? - So I'm Ku Phelps.
Look.
- Gosh, how long are your arms? - Look.
By the way, their bellies are touching, not their chests.
Their arms... Look at them. A fist could fit in there.
Look at them. There's space between your chests.
- Let's see. - Look.
There's this much space.
No wonder. It didn't feel pleasant.
- Right? I bet it was unpleasant. - It was weird.
- This is just a simple test. - Okay.
Don't do it right away. How many push-ups can you do?
I can do 5 sets of 20 repetitions.
(It's a total of 100 push-ups.)
- You can do 20 in 1 set? - I can do 20.
Can you do it with a clap?
I've never tried that.
Let me demonstrate. This is the proper form.
- Slowly. A negative push-up. - Can he clap?
- One, two. - Twenty negative push-ups?
(Bumping)
- What is that? - You'll break your chin.
Do you have to smash...
- your chin too? - Right.
(Embarrassed)
- It goes like this. - Is your chin okay?
Try it. But...
- You can't do it with your chin. - No.
He said he was fine.
We're the athletic guys.
(We're the athletic guys, not manly guys.)
But no fooling around.
- I've never tried this before. - Okay. No fooling around.
Two.
- He's doing it. - Yes, he's doing it.
- Great. - He's better than you.
It didn't touch...
Okay.
- Are you done sizing me up? - Yes. You're better...
- Okay. That should do it. - This is pretty tough.
- It's tough, right? - Marcus.
- Okay. All right. - Yes.
- Okay. - Grab them.
(They begin the workout routine in earnest.)
Here I go. One.
That's tough.
- Your form is nice. - My gosh.
Seven, eight,
nine, ten.
One, two, three,
- Darn it. - four...
Wait.
You could hurt your back.
(Let me help you, Sung Hwan.)
Your gaze...
(I wanted to be a cool guy.)
Hey, Marcus.
(In reality, he's doing physical therapy with Seon Min.)
Two, three, four.
Five. Hey, Marcus.
(You can do this!)
Six...
Last one.
(He barely manages to finish thanks to Min's encouragement.)
Hey, Marcus.
That's it?
(Grunting)
This is crazy.
All right, Sung Hwan.
(Don't talk to me!)
Sung Hwan.
You only did one set.
Gosh, I can't breathe.
(Struggling to breathe)
- He was showing off before this. - Should I go for it?
All right.
(He barely manages to get up.)
I get that this might be tough on you. Let me catch up with you.
- It's because I weigh 100kg now. - Okay.
Wait.
- Are you all right? - Go ahead. Do it.
- Go? Okay. - Okay.
(Seon Min is ready to follow him after checking his condition.)
Ten, right?
One. Go lower.
- Three. - You're quite strong.
- His technique... - Seon Min is good.
Look at his physique. You can tell he works out.
He's good.
(He's pretty good.)
(Getting up)
Gosh, his movements are light.
(Exhaling)
(After he exhales...)
He can do it.
(He continues the routine in a more stable manner.)
(Go for it.)
- He's sitting down again. - He's about to pass out.
(Boosting up down to the last one)
(He finishes the routine without Sung Hwan's help.)
He was pretty fit.
It was nice.
My postures were better, though.
I saw him work out on the mountain before.
And I watched him work out today. He was quite good.
He was good at squats too. He was great.
Go.
(I can't back down now.)
(With sheer determination and willpower)
(Burning off the calories they'll consume later)
You got it.
You got it. Come on.
They made a good excuse to eat.
(Laughing)
There you go.
(He completes 3 sets in the end.)
I need to lie down.
My goodness.
(Gosh, I'm dying.)
What a nice workout.
(Seon Min lies down just like Sung Hwan.)
I'm annoyed because it's like a scene from a youth comic series.
My goodness.
(Breathing hard)
Their bellies look the same.
(Belly decalcomania)
Mount Bukhan and Mount Gwanak.
(Two big mountains of the bodyweight workout)
- It was great. - It was great.
It was great indeed.
(They climb down together...)
(after reaching the summit of waist circumference.)
Gosh, my legs.
(Staggering)
I'll wash up and wait.
Okay.
(They wash off their sweat.)
I feel so refreshed.
(Clean)
(Snoring)
Sung Hwan.
(He fell asleep while waiting for Seon Min.)
He looks like their baby.
(Waa)
Their baby.
- It's cool, right? - It's so cool.
Where should I put this?
You can put it outside. Just throw it.
- Outside? - By the door.
(Heave-ho)
My goodness.
- Are your dirty clothes here? - Yes.
All right. My goodness.
What are you doing?
- I'm doing the laundry. - Okay.
You told me...
- that my place smelled nice. - Yes.
It's thanks to a laundry sanitizer.
To eliminate odor, you need to kill odor-causing bacteria.
If you use it,
- you won't smell like sweat. - It's the most important.
- It smells nice. - This is how I eliminate odor.
You just need to put it in the fabric softener section.
It's so easy to use.
It looks very convenient.
(You're right.)
- You're thirsty, right? - My throat is parched.
Okay. Let's drink...
- Sikhye? - what we bought earlier.
There are my favorite cups.
Okay.
Is he scratching his head?
- Isn't it refreshing? - It's for hair loss prevention.
It's so nice.
(Setting up sikhye while Seon Min scratches his head)
Sit down.
These cups are really nice when you need one sip.
(Pouring)
(How nice.)
Take it.
It must be cold.
Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you for coming.
It's perfect. Thank you for your hard work.
(Clinking)
- My goodness. - Gosh.
It was perfect.
Isn't it delicious?
- Hey. - One more glass?
(Shall we have one more glass?)
- Calm down. - Calm down?
- Okay. Thank you. - Calm down.
- It's so nice. - A sweet drink is nice.
That's what I love about working out.
It's nice to enjoy the cool wind after sweating.
You're living the life I want.
Really?
- You guys had good chemistry... - Yes.
- before I came. - That's right.
Shin Young, were you recording a radio show?
I had to record about six episodes...
- that day. - I bet you arrived late.
I arrived a bit late.
We need to get ready.
I want you to do something for me. Stay seated.
- I'll help. - You need to stay seated to help.
- Stay seated? - Yes. Hold on.
- I love doing something like this. - Okay.
I love doing something fun like this.
For a second...
- What... - Is your handwriting any good?
I can't write because of an arm injury.
I entered a handwriting contest in Korea...
- and placed eighth. - A handwriting contest.
A handwriting contest?
- You placed eighth? - Yes.
I was in third grade.
(It was about 30 years ago.)
Wasn't that too long ago?
- I still have that talent. - Okay. Firstly...
(Handing over)
- Write here. - Okay.
(Write it.)
M, E, N, U.
- M, E, N, U. Menu. - Menu.
- Menu. - Write in English, "Menu."
- Okay. - Menu.
Sung Hwan loves decorating.
I love such mise-en-scene.
(That's right.)
Appetizer.
- Can I write it in Korean? - No, write it in English.
(Flustered)
(Appetizer?)
- Appe... - It starts with A.
- No, it's E. - E.
- You read A as "Ah." - Okay.
- It's E, P, I... - E, P...
He forgot the spelling.
(In that case)
- E... I think it's E. - E.
- It's E. - It's E, P...
Are you going with the pronunciation?
I got confused for a second.
- E, P, I... - E, P, I...
(He continues to get the spelling wrong.)
Do you know how to spell...
- "Appetizer?" - They all wouldn't know.
Do you know it? Does anyone in here know it?
Who knows the exact spelling?
(Staring)
(Everyone looks at the English literature major.)
I know it.
- I know it. - Go ahead.
I don't know it.
Don't you know it?
- I'll be impressed if someone does. - Don't you know it?
- A, P, P, I... - P, P, I?
It's A, P, P, E.
- Is it A, P, P, E? - That's right. It's E.
Not I?
It's pretty confusing.
I think you should be studying, not eating.
It's like what your mom says.
"How could you eat at this moment?"
(Laughing)
That's what I love about I Live Alone.
I always learn something new.
- But I forget. - You forget.
- You need to remember it. - Sung Hwan.
- Shall we write it? - Let's write it.
- It's a marker. I can't erase it. - Okay.
- E, P. - E, P, A?
- I. - I.
Ta.
T, A...
- T... - I don't think it's T, A.
It's "Ta," right?
- Epita... - E...
Just erase it and write it in Korean.
Just erase it.
Okay.
- Let's call it a performance. - Okay.
- E... - That explains the erased part.
Is it "E" in Korean?
- It doesn't matter. - It doesn't matter.
Appetizer.
When you try to write it,
- it gets confusing. - That's right.
Even Americans mess up the spelling.
That's right.
- Under "Appetizer..." - Appetizer.
Okay.
- Mexican. - Mexican.
Yes. Mexican.
- Mexican. - Yes. Mexican.
You had a menu in mind.
What comes after the appetizer?
The main event.
"The main event?" Do people say that?
- "The main event?" - The main event.
- What is it called? - Highlight.
- Staple. - No.
"Highlight?"
- Main. - Main.
Main. Marcus, I did it.
- Main dish. - Main dish.
- What does it mean? - "Dish" is a meal.
Okay.
"Dish" is a meal.
Eumseong.
The menu contains a quiz.
Doenjang jjigae. You...
Okay.
Don't write anything else. Just write "Doenjang jjigae."
- And put "Sindang-dong" under it. - Okay.
Plus "East Sea."
- "Sindang-dong" plus... - "East Sea."
"East Sea." Okay.
- It'll be delicious. - Here.
"Sindang-dong" and "East Sea?"
- I can't figure it out. - It's like a code.
- A code. - Then we'll need a rest.
- Put "Seongsu-dong." - "Seongsu-dong?"
- Does something come to mind? - Hold on.
- "Seongsu-dong?" - Seongsu-dong.
Seongsu-dong.
(Curious)
- Now, - Okay.
this is important.
Like I said, I love such mise-en-scene.
- I see. - You know what I mean, right?
When the guest comes, she'll see the menu.
It's like fine dining.
- It's like fine dining. - Yes.
- It looks classy, Sung Hwan. - Right?
- Let's hurry up and get ready. - Okay.
- Help me by my side. - Okay.
(The menu he made with care goes on the table.)
- I loved the care he put into it. - Okay. It's set.
(Let's hurry up and cook.)
Okay. It's set.
(Sung Hwan enters the kitchen.)
(Following)
How can I help you?
I want you to peel some potatoes.
Potatoes.
Here.
- Okay. - Here.
- Okay. - Put on an apron.
Okay.
- The two of you go along well. - We go along well.
Hold on.
(Taking out)
(He spots the potatoes.)
Okay.
- Shall I peel all of them? - Let's peel three.
I cook as well.
Seon Min is good at cooking.
(While living alone for 19 years,)
(he has learned to cook all sorts of dishes.)
That's right. Seon Min is good at cooking.
All right.
(He'll show off his skills to Sung Hwan.)
It feels strange to cook here with you.
(I can't believe I'm cooking here with you.)
- It's an honor, Sung Hwan. - The honor is mine.
- Chef. - My goodness.
- Please teach me many things. - My goodness.
- Into the stainless steel bowl. - Okay.
(He doesn't want to do disservice to the chef.)
(Full of passion)
- Is this good enough? - It's perfect.
It's perfect, right?
- The kitchen is cramped. - These are...
Gosh, it's completely full.
These are sea squirts.
(Impressed)
This is insane.
(Many ingredients)
Seeing the ingredients...
made me look forward to dinnertime.
- I can get a sense of it. - Yes.
- The concept has a natural vibe. - That's right.
They look good in the kitchen...
- together. - I know.
(Right?)
Let's eliminate any odor.
- He is good at cooking. - Yes.
Just a little bit.
(Sung Hwan blanches the ingredients.)
- One at a time? - Yes.
Okay.
They look tasty.
Seon Min assisted me perfectly by my side.
- I wasn't half bad, right? - Cooking didn't take much time.
That's how it is.
I love their bromance.
(Heavy chemistry)
- All done. - Sung Hwan,
you could open a pub.
My goodness.
- Let's prepare it. - Let's do that.
If the two of them open a pub,
- it'll be very successful. - I'll go to their restaurant.
That's right. If I happen to look at the kitchen...
while passing by...
- and see such owners, - Let's say they're the owners.
- I'll go in no matter what. - No matter what.
It doesn't matter what the menu is.
I bet the restaurant will be closed four days a week.
- Due to the lack of stamina. - We'll drink every time.
We'll eat all the remaining food.
- They'll eat all of it. - They'll rest as much as they want.
They'll only open the place for eight hours at a time.
All right.
(They work hard on the opening.)
(Knocking)
Hold on. Young must be here.
- Young? - Who is it?
- Young? - Young?
Young! Min!
Young?
Min, Hwan, and Young sound a bit freaky.
Why do you say that, KUN?
They have romantic-sounding names.
Sung Hwan.
- Sung Hwan. Hurry. - Oh, my.
Young.
Sung Hwan.
- Sung Hwan. Hurry. - Oh, my.
Young.
- Sung Hwan. - What's this?
My friend, Young is here.
Kim Shin Young.
My goodness.
(Panting)
Young, here.
- Young, sit down. - There is no elevator.
- Sung Hwan. - Sit down.
You should earn a lot of money and get an elevator.
Sit down.
- This one is new. - It's new.
What's all this?
(In tatters)
(She carried the luggage from the ground level.)
Gosh, I brought so many things.
Heave-ho.
(Stopping after one floor)
- I nearly died. - Her bags were heavy.
- That was how you came. - The bags...
(Panting)
My goodness.
It's about to rip.
(Save me.)
It's new.
- What's this? - What's all this?
Why did you bring so many things?
What's inside?
Hold on.
- You make me look bad. - Sung Hwan.
(His eyes are fixed on the bag.)
- Sung Hwan, spare me a glance. - My goodness.
- Welcome. - Seriously.
- She is right. - I couldn't believe it.
- Seriously. - It wasn't like that.
- He turned his back on her. - Hold on.
- Sung Hwan, you're too much. - He didn't see me.
Their eyes were fixed on the bags.
- My goodness. - Welcome.
- Hey. - My arms hurt so much.
I did it without thinking.
Seriously. This is impressive.
My goodness. I mean...
This is incredible.
- Oh, my. - It's for the windows.
- What's that? - The window-cleaning tool?
It's the window-cleaning tool.
(Young's new item, curved mop)
It's the window-cleaning tool you saw once.
(I really want it, to be honest!)
- It's new. - Thanks.
It's new. I bought two as a set.
- She told us about it. - I threw away one.
- You brought so many things. - Here.
- Yes. - What's this?
I'm the younger one.
- My goodness. - This is incredible.
It's a snack you can enjoy...
- with beer. - Thank you.
I'm so moved by this item.
- I'm so moved. - Here.
This snack is insane.
(Presents pour out endlessly.)
I brought clothing for you.
- I told you about it. - This is insane.
It's sunspray.
- Don't turn your face white. - You're right.
- Use it for your face. - I used it today.
- This is body cream. - Cream.
- Body cream. - My skin is so dry. Look at this.
That's right. Your skin has always been dry.
She brought all the items she promised to give me.
- Unbelievable. - This is for Seon Min.
- Really? - I put his name on it. Seon Min.
- Here. - Are all of these mine?
- Thanks. - She brought items for me too.
Thanks, Shin Young.
- Unbelievable. - I told you so.
Yes, you did.
(She even wrote the recipient's name.)
- This is incredible. - Thanks.
- Use them. - There are so many items.
- Seriously. - Are all of these mine?
- Thanks. Thank you so much. - I...
- Young is like that. - Here.
It's for the sweaty back and feet.
- Does it keep you dry? - Yes. I know that you sweat a lot.
It's an item for sweating. We sweat a lot.
When I sit next to CODE KUNST, I don't feel very hot.
But when Sung Hwan and I sit next to each other, I feel very hot.
I gave him an item for sweating so that we wouldn't sweat.
It gets really hot.
When I had gamtae, Sung Hwan was really jealous of me.
So I brought him gamtae as well.
I gave him all the items I had saved up.
This is a shirt from Shin Young.
- I see. - Really?
- And try smelling me. - Why...
Why are you reacting like that?
- Don't I smell like lotion? - You smell nice.
- See? - You smell like...
- baby powder. - It smells like baby powder.
She gave me everything. She even gave me...
- a facial spray. - Really?
To be honest, I had saved up...
the items in a ziplock bag.
- You had saved them up. - Yes.
We teased her about...
how she should actually give us those items.
- She had saved them up. - She had saved up all of them.
- I remembered. - One at a time.
- Seriously. - How nice.
It's so much work to pack them 1 by 1.
- I was joking. - The house is cramped.
- I'll use it. Seriously. Thank you. - Clean the windows.
I'll clean the windows.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Here. - Talk among yourselves.
The stove is on. Let me go and add an ingredient.
- Okay. - Stay here.
Let me go and add an ingredient.
(Min and Young, get some rest.)
- Shall I clean the windows? - Try it.
I tried to use it at home and failed.
Let me try it.
He has more strength.
I figured that I might lack the strength.
- I know. This item... - Do I need to assemble it?
You need to assemble it.
I'll put it inside.
If I do it right away, it'll splatter.
(He adds boiled chicken feet to the pan.)
I didn't know that you could cook chicken feet at home.
This is insane.
- The chicken feet dish looks good. - I know.
(Spicy stir-fried chicken feet)
The smoky flavor is no joke.
- He knows how to cook. He's great. - So that's how you make it.
This is incredible.
Okay.
(Coughing)
- Sung Hwan, it smells spicy. - It smells spicy.
No, it isn't spicy.
It smells really spicy.
(The spicy smoke makes her cough a lot.)
My goodness.
- Are you okay? - It's gas!
Hey, open the window.
- Sung Hwan. - My goodness.
(Young writhes in pain.)
- Are you okay? - Someone save me!
My goodness.
Hey, take care of Shin Young.
Gosh, I won't come back here.
(Sniffling)
Sung Hwan, why did you cook poison?
(Nervous Shin Young and relaxed Sung Hwan)
Sung Hwan, can I go home?
What are you talking about?
(The Chunk Trio has finally assembled.)
(Shall we eat in earnest?)
(They stuff their faces.)
(Big chunks of meat charm the Chunk Trio.)
(Eating without hesitation)
(The Chunk Trio doesn't stop.)
(I Live Alone)
(Looking around)
(Ji Hyeon heads out in the morning.)
(But no matter where you look)
Hold on. Where is he?
Wait. I don't think he is in Korea.
I'm in Shanghai, China.
- Shanghai. - Shanghai.
- I lived in Shanghai as a child. - Really?
I wanted to revisit my neighborhood.
My goodness.
I also had someone to meet.
So I came here for a vacation.
(He revisited Shanghai after many years.)
For how many years did you live there?
I lived there from 4th to 6th grade.
- About two years? - Yes.
- About two years. - Two to three years.
(He spent his precious childhood in Shanghai.)
(It has been a while.)
(He revisits his childhood memories...)
(as he explores the streets of Shanghai.)
This feels a bit like Shanghai Old Street.
(The neighborhood still has people's warmth.)
- The place hasn't changed much. - Really?
It's where the locals live.
It's nice.
I think I know what it is.
Old-fashioned.
Old-fashioned...
jianbing.
(What are people waiting for in a line early in the morning?)
It's the dish I love the most,
- egg jianbing. - Egg jianbing?
Similar Korean dishes would be hotteok...
- or egg bread. - That's right.
It's something like that.
You make the batter with flour and eggs.
Then you add a bit of vegetables...
and sausages.
- It's so tasty. - It's...
- crispy... - That's right. The filling.
- and moist. That's right. - That's right.
It's so tasty.
When I lived in China,
I often ate egg jianping for breakfast.
How cute!
- He was chubby. That's cute. - That was when I was in China.
This is the way to determine a good egg jianbing place.
It must be sold on the street.
It can't be sold at the department store.
It's good when made on the spot by spinning the dough.
I can tell right away.
(Peeking)
Okay.
- Gosh. - That place is still there.
- It looks delicious. - Okay.
I really wanted that.
(Excited to the max)
- He looks excited. - Gosh.
It smells great.
(At the thought of getting to have some jianbing...)
He became an elementary school student.
It was something he had when he was a kid.
He must have missed it so much.
Are you from Korea?
You're an influencer?
Are you a star?
(Star?)
(Smiling)
(Country Mouse Ji Hyeon's fantasy for a long time)
(Being suspected as a celebrity)
(He has been keeping that dream for a while.)
- It's the moment you talked about. - Right.
- That was what you wanted. - Right.
- "Are you a star?" - You're an influencer?
- Are you a star? - Oh, yes.
"Was it that obvious?"
Are you a movie star or a singer?
- I'm a singer. - Singer?
- Singer. - Singer.
Thank you.
After buying this shirt, I thought it was too intense,
so I kept it in the closet for around two years.
But Sung Woo told me to make a lot of challenges.
I never saw him wear...
- fancy colors. - Right.
I think that helped me become bold.
(He finally got asked if he was a celebrity in Shanghai.)
I felt very grateful.
I should've found him some summer clothes as well.
- Thank you. - I'm from Qingdao.
- Qingdao? - I'm from Qingdao.
- You are traveling to Shanghai? - Yes.
- Do you know how to speak Chinese? - Yes. A little.
- A little? - Yes.
Gosh, his pronunciation is great.
This is an old store, right?
Yes. A traditional old store.
A traditional old store.
When I was young,
I lived here for around two years.
That was when I tried the egg jianbing.
(He speaks in Chinese freely.)
Your Chinese is much better...
- than I thought. - Really?
Don't you tend to forget a language if you don't use it?
I remembered how to say things little by little.
You two are able to talk with each other.
(The small talk carries on.)
He must remember it as he learned the language when he was young.
- Right. - Right.
When do you head back to Qingdao?
I return after eating this.
- Really? Today? - Yes.
(It's their first time seeing each other,)
(but they enjoy a good chat.)
You must've felt excited to speak after a while.
Right. I started to talk naturally.
It's been a while since you spoke Chinese.
Right.
(Their turns came quickly as they waited together.)
- Gosh! - Gosh! This is China!
(He catches everyone's attention...)
(with his overwhelming presence.)
- He's... - Hold on. Lee Seon Min!
That's my junior!
(Due to the shock of the talent show...)
- It's like he's singing that song. - Right.
- You've got a friend in me - All of the men...
walk around like that in the summer.
- Right. - Their bellies are out like this.
- Right. - Right.
- Right. - I've only heard of that.
(Peeking)
(What should I get?)
- That looks delicious. - A, B, C, D, E.
- Including the sauce, - Tenderloin?
- there are so many kinds. - What is that?
Are you going to get A?
- I'm going to get B. - B?
I had the ones like B when I was young.
(He chooses B, the one with the crust.)
That gives it a good texture.
- It must have that. - Right.
- It has to have that crunch. - Right.
(It looks amazing.)
I'll pay for it.
- Gosh! - He's going to pay for it?
- It's fine! - It's okay!
(He strongly refuses with his hands.)
- It doesn't cost that much! - It's fine!
- It doesn't cost that much! - That's amazing.
He's so kind.
(He ends up ordering Ji Hyeon's as well.)
- Gosh, that's impressive. - That man said it was fine...
as he was an owner of a trading company.
- Really? - Yes.
He must've enjoyed the conversation he had with you.
Right.
He fell for his charms in that brief moment.
Can't I buy it for you?
No! I'll pay!
Thank you.
(He wasn't able to go against the older brother's decision.)
Okay.
Thank you.
(The jianbings that were ordered come out 1 by 1.)
- Gosh, he's impressive. - He paid for it.
Thank you!
(Bye.)
- This is a kind of friendship. - Right.
Can I eat here?
(He sits down on a bench nearby.)
Gosh, this brings me back to the old days.
(Peeking)
Does it taste good?
- Does it taste good? - How cute.
- She's having pig trotters. - She's having pig trotters.
(He sits next to the children freely enjoying pig trotters.)
This is the real deal.
- Gosh, that looks delicious. - Right on the bench.
That looks so good.
(Let's give it a try.)
(Taking a big bite)
(Truly happy)
He's loving it.
- The food is... - That's the face...
Ji Hyeon makes when he's happy.
- It's been a while since I had it. - It's the exact taste.
It was the same taste from what I had in the past.
What does it taste like?
It's like a very thin and soft pajeon.
It does feel like a pajeon.
The sauce is doubanjiang.
- I can't imagine its taste. - Doubanjiang?
- Everyone will like that. - Right.
It's a taste that anyone would like.
- Right. - Right.
(He gets to try it after around 20 years.)
(Young Ji Hyeon's favorite food)
Food works as a time capsule.
- Right. - It moves you back in time.
It was so good.
(Smirking)
Gosh, it really feels like I'm in China now.
It's been a while.
His face shows that he has gone back in time.
You had it when you were around their age, right?
- Yes. - The jianbing.
- I was slightly older than them. - Right.
(He calmly enjoys his breakfast.)
- Gosh. - Gosh, is this "Chungking Express?"
Hold on! What is this?
(It's like a movie scene.)
It looks great.
(It looks great.)
(Shoving in)
(He finished the jianbing in a flash.)
(Sucking)
(He sets off again after filling his stomach.)
Gosh, I'm full.
(I'm full now.)
(Looking around)
Hair salon.
Should I cut my hair?
What?
It's ten yuan for a haircut.
(The hair salons in town are open early in the morning.)
(He heads to a hair salon.)
Are you really going to cut your hair?
I had an important appointment coming up.
- I see. - I went to cut my hair.
- Gosh. - Should I get a brief haircut?
Hello.
- Can I get a haircut? - Yes.
(He enters a hair salon nearby.)
Gosh, it's fascinating to see a Chinese hair salon.
(He moves to get his hair washed first.)
I got my head shaved when I was young.
I had haircuts on the streets.
- The streets? - Yes.
There were people who did haircuts on the street.
- Just like that. - I see.
- I think I've seen that before. - Right.
There were men who did haircuts on the streets.
I often got haircuts from them.
That was how I got my haircuts in China.
(A lot of time has passed...)
(and he will try getting a haircut in an indoor salon.)
Please don't make it too short.
- Not too short? - Right.
- Just a trim? - Right.
A trim.
His hair looks nice.
- It's a nice style, isn't it? - It's a nice style.
(Stylish)
(Taking a look)
(His eyes change as soon as he starts.)
(Falling)
(His hands move without hesitation...)
(and his hair gets sorted quickly.)
It looks nice.
He's got great skills.
(Amazed)
It feels like getting a haircut at a shop in Korea.
- He's great. - It's neat.
It's an important day for me.
I have an important appointment.
(An important day?)
(Blowing)
(After hearing that it's an important day for him,)
(the master's hands move even faster.)
- What is this? - What is this?
- What is this? - Is this "Surprise Mystery TV?"
Hold on! Isn't this "TTS?"
"True and True Story!"
It's "True and True Story!"
- "False!" - "False!"
(A masterpiece is being made with his unbelievable skills.)
This is exactly that.
"The Man With a Flower" from the past.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
(Shanghai's Gu Jun Pyo)
You have wings on both sides now.
- He can fly now. - You look good.
(Make me your honorary barber.)
It looks nice.
- Gosh. - He checked from behind...
if he was satisfied with it.
- I didn't know he was watching. - The Shanghai style.
I love it. Thank you so much.
(Feeling proud)
(Whistling)
(Shanghai's Gu Jun Pyo walks the streets again.)
What's this?
- What is this place? - Gosh.
What is this place?
Is it a park?
(Has a large crowd gathered to see Shanghai's Gu Jun Pyo?)
- What is this place? - Gosh.
What is this place?
Is it a park?
(The park is filled with a large crowd.)
(Between the large crowd,)
(there are sheets of paper on the floor?)
I thought it was some kind of event,
but it turned out to be a matchmaking process.
- Matchmaking? - What?
They're all matchmakers.
- Right. - Gosh.
There was a woman who was 51 years old.
(A 51-year-old civil servant)
She's a 51-year-old civil servant.
One of the requirements is to be a Shanghai native.
That's nice.
- She was born in 1980. - She's unmarried.
She's a designer from Shanghai.
She's okay with a five-year age gap, older or younger.
She cannot meet a man...
- with a bad temper. - A five-year age gap.
A five-year age gap older or younger.
There was one born in 1977.
(Born in 1977, unmarried)
Hold on. Born in 1977?
- Hyun Moo! - I'm watching carefully.
She's from Shanghai.
She has decent looks with a decent salary.
She's looking for an unmarried man...
who was born between 1975 and 1983.
He must look and act neatly...
and must not have bad hobbies.
You don't have bad hobbies.
- Hello. - Hello.
(He took care of his looks...)
(even when he ran as if his ears fell off.)
(He's also a big spender.)
Just like a xiaolongbao.
(Moomoo is rich with trendy hobbies.)
(Are we meant to be?)
It might be a good match.
I fail with "over 175cm."
I'm 173cm.
There are only three lines about herself.
- Right. - There are...
- so many requirements in blue. - There are so many requirements.
(They were 2cm apart from meeting each other.)
There were those around my age as well.
There were young people born in 2002 and 2003 as well.
This is really fascinating.
- It's an unusual sight. - It's fascinating.
There were people from all ages.
- There were people around my age. - Right.
There were those born in 2003 and 2004 as well.
Gosh, it's my first time seeing this.
(The park matchmaking is an unusual sight even to Ji Hyeon.)
Is this where marriages take place?
- Arranged marriages. - Arranged marriages.
(It's a place for arranged marriages.)
Can I meet the person if I want to?
Gosh!
- We're the parents. - Really?
(It's possible because they're the parents.)
- You're the parents? - So most of the parents come out...
- for their children, right? - Right.
That's how it's done.
They're there to find the right partners for their children.
(Fascinated)
- Right. - Right.
So their parents are out here to find their partners.
My goodness.
- Aren't they so enthusiastic? - That's fascinating.
The parents meet each other even before things start.
You said it was an important day.
- Were you there to find a match? - Hold on.
Was that...
- why you got your hair done? - That's not it!
You got your hair done as it was an important day.
- That's not it. - His eyes were shining brightly...
- when he did your hair. - That's not it.
Did you get your hair done to look good for the parents?
- But... - Gosh.
Would I have gone to China to look for a wife?
His T-shirt is too fancy for that.
Or he could be there to look for his first love.
That's not it!
(That's not it!)
(Shall I read some of them?)
What year were you born in?
(What year were you born in?)
I was born in 1995.
You look much younger.
- Gosh, she's interested! - Gosh!
- She found you! - She must've liked you!
- Watch out. - You're on her radar!
Gosh, that's amazing.
She had a close look at me.
Are you looking for someone for yourself?
(Another matchmaker)
I was just looking around.
I'm at the age of marrying someone as well.
(He gets a lot of matchmaking inquiries.)
- This is street casting. - Right.
- Right. It's street casting. - This is street casting.
(He finds a quiet place to avoid the street casting.)
(Peeking)
(A man watches Ji Hyeon carefully.)
- Where are you from? - I'm from Korea.
I'm from Korea.
Korea.
(What's going on?)
Arirang
(Arirang)
("Arirang" gets sung out of nowhere.)
- Gosh. - There are those people at parks.
There's always someone like him.
(A street audition opens out of nowhere.)
(Am I dreaming?)
(Going away through the Arirang Pass)
(Arirang Pass)
He's Shanghai's Jukebox.
How do you know this song?
(He sings another right away.)
- Gosh! - Gosh! It's "Lady of Soyang Lake!"
(The lesser cuckoo cries sadly)
(Chirp)
He's spot on!
(A touching chirp from the man of China)
(She fills me with worry)
(The Lady of Soyang Lake)
- How does he know this one? - He sang "Lady of Soyang Lake."
- How does he know it so well? - Gosh.
And he leaves just like that. Right!
- That's how parks are! - Thank you.
(He's on cloud nine.)
He felt like a master.
This place is exciting.
- This place is so exciting. - Right.
Many fascinating things happened to me.
It feels new to me even though I go there often.
- Many fascinating things happen. - Right.
(He leaves the park after his fascinating experiences.)
(Approaching)
I'm here.
A bike?
- Is it a public bike? - Yes.
I found it while walking, and it reminded me of the old days.
(He sets off with the bike he found.)
(Looking around)
This is it. This small bridge.
Okay.
This is it.
(He found a familiar bridge from his past memory.)
(Happy to see it)
Gosh, it has really been a while.
I remember this place.
It feels like watching a teen film.
Right.
It's Newstar!
- Gosh! - Newstar?
- What is that? - Awesome!
- It's a sauna. - It's a spa?
- A Korean sauna? - Gosh.
It was a new place that was made when I lived there.
(Around 20 years ago)
That place was revolutionary back then.
- I understand what you're saying. - It was revolutionary.
- I get it. - Right.
There were spas and TVs.
It was unheard of.
- There are places like that. - Right.
It was the hot place in town.
The real estate agency.
I'm planning to head toward the area I lived in.
(Into the area he lived in when he was young)
Gosh, it's my school!
- The school you went to? - Gosh!
- Your school? - They have grass now.
I'm curious to see it.
They have grass now.
(It's been so long since I've seen my school.)
You went to your school?
- Gosh. - Did he come for his first love?
It's way better now.
(He parks the bike in front of the school.)
(He walks over like a student going to school.)
I really wanted to visit that school.
(Ji Hyeon walks past the open gate.)
(He visits his school after 20 years.)
Awesome!
- Gosh! - What?
- Check out the track! - There's even a track!
I attended there from when I was 11 years old to 13 years old.
It's Sang Hong Middle School.
As it was the weekend, there were residents playing sports.
I went in as the gate was open.
That track.
That track must be used for a run.
(Gosh, I'm here again.)
It must feel strange.
It's my classroom!
- Really? - Yes.
- Where? - It's gotten a lot better.
The board has changed.
(The inside has changed, but it's still in the same place.)
(After seeing the class after a long time...)
(Hopping)
(32-year-old Ji Hyeon has gone back to his childhood days.)
Here...
(Goodness)
I bought strawberry shakes here during lunchtime.
It was a nice school to sell strawberry shakes.
It brings back memories.
You decide whether the school is nice or not by a strawberry shake.
MINHO only checks out the track,
and she only cares about a strawberry shake.
They only see and hear the things they want to see and hear.
I mean, what kind of school sells strawberry shakes?
- Right, there's none. - It's perfect.
(It must be delicious.)
It brings back memories.
(Feeling nostalgic)
The alley leading to the snack bar was the same.
Why did it feel so high when I was young?
I get what he means.
I went up to the floor of my elementary school...
that had classes for grades 5 and 6.
In my memory,
- That's right. - the classroom was huge.
"Why is it so small?"
And you can climb over the back gate wall really easily.
- I was really surprised. - Right.
Like vaulting over the vaulting horse.
The lady owner would send down an envelope for money,
and I'd put a certain amount of money inside.
Then she'd lower food for us.
Sometimes, she'd just throw them.
I was really scared to catch the food then.
- But... - It must've been thrilling.
But the girl I really liked...
bought a strawberry shake.
- You gave it to her? - Since I was a boy,
she asked me to get it for her...
when I couldn't catch it well.
So I confidently caught it,
- but half of it burst. - Oh, no.
Because I grabbed it too hard.
I remember giving it to her like that.
Oh, no.
When you're young, you fall in love with someone...
if you see them more than three times.
If they smile at you more than two times,
- they become your first love. - That's love.
(If they smile at you more than two times, they're your first love.)
(Smiling)
(Waving)
(Saying goodbye to the backdoor of the snack bar)
(Chuckling)
(He leaves the school carrying old memories.)
(After leaving the school he hasn't seen years,)
(he's back on the road.)
(Looking around)
Wait. It looked something like this.
- What? - What is it?
It's somewhere near here.
What? What is it?
It looked something like that.
I found the spot where my parents...
used to have a shop.
- Your parents had a shop? - Yes, they did.
They ran various businesses in China,
but at first,
- they sold accessories. - They did.
After that, they sold gimbap and tteokbokki.
Both shops did really well.
So they gained confidence...
and opened a big Korean cuisine restaurant.
- That was the cause, right? - Yes.
- So you came back after two years. - Yes.
- Oh, really? - It must've not been easy.
- Oh, no. - Thinking back,
I remember my mom crying every day.
- You had a difficult time. - Because it was hard?
We went completely bankrupt and returned to Korea.
They went completely bankrupt, but his parents...
were really nice to the staff members.
They paid their staff on time. It was never delayed.
- They were such nice owners. - You really know everything.
- I know. - He's my only son.
(The son is moved.)
It is here.
Wait.
(Is it near here?)
I think this is the place.
This is it.
Wait. He must've found it.
It became a hair salon.
It turned into a hair salon.
(Staring)
The business is doing well.
(Staring at it silently)
I should've cut my hair here.
(Excuse me...)
(He plucks up his courage and approaches the staff.)
I used to live here.
So I was looking at the shop.
How long has it been since you opened the hair salon?
- Ten years. - Ten years?
I asked them how long it's been since they opened their salon,
and they said it's been ten years.
Before that, there was a bank...
and a convenience store before that.
So I realized how much time had passed.
If it was 20 years ago,
my dad was around 42 or 43.
- He was my age then. - My mom was in her late 30s.
- Around 39 or 40? - They were amazing.
My parents took on a big challenge...
at such a young age.
Running businesses in another country.
I wouldn't have been able to do it.
So I think my parents are amazing.
People from my parents' generation are all amazing.
They had such a tough life.
They're amazing.
Right. They bet their lives on it.
It's hard to bet your life on something at my age.
It's hard.
(It has become a hair salon.)
(Glancing back)
He's having mixed emotions.
- He has mixed emotions. - It got him thinking.
(He has mixed feelings for no reason.)
(Smiling)
(It was a good thing I decided to come here.)
(Ji Hyeon keeps walking around his old neighborhood.)
(Surprised)
Who knew this area would get so crowded?
The Korean Wave is sweeping this area as well.
- "Seoul Night Market?" - "Seoul Night Market?"
- "Hello?" - It's a Koreatown.
A Koreatown?
(He's arrived at a Koreatown.)
Gosh, it's nice.
(Looking around)
There were a few Korean restaurants...
and Korean pubs in that area. But now...
- The signs are all in Korean. - They're all in Korean.
(A place where diverse Korean cultures were introduced)
It's where I went with my family to have Korean food.
- It's a penny bun. It's... - They have a penny bun?
It's what we had at Golgulsa Temple.
(They had it at Golgulsa Temple in Gyeongju.)
It made it to China as well.
There are so many things.
It seemed to have developed a lot in 20 years.
It became a tourist spot.
Only Koreans used to go there...
to get Korean ingredients.
There's an escalator too.
- It's fascinating. - It's huge.
It looks like an old-style Korean shopping arcade.
- The early days of Doota. - That's right.
- You're right. It's that vibe. - It's that vibe.
- It has that vibe. - This place is fun.
(He walks straight on as though he's familiar with the place.)
This is nice.
Has this place been always this big?
I didn't know it was this big back then.
(Let's see.)
"City-style Menswear."
- "City-style Menswear." - "City-style Menswear."
It looks amazing.
I wanted to dress...
like a successful man...
- for the appointment later. - Oh, really?
Yes.
Oh, he's getting clothes.
(Ji Hyeon went into the shop to buy new clothes.)
Since he learned from CODE KUNST,
- he can pick on his own. - I'm anxious about him going solo.
You feel anxious every time he touches something, right?
- He said that shirt was amazing. - Why...
He only took lesson one.
- He has to take lesson three. - Wait.
Take a look.
- It's seriously fine. - Okay.
- I'll look forward to it. - A city-style menswear.
Since he learned from you, he'll remember the lesson.
(Recalling the lesson he learned from his fashion guru)
Shall I pick some clothes?
(Amazed)
This is Sung Woo's style.
(Watching carefully)
(The sleeveless shirt and shirt that CODE KUNST picked for him)
It's a totally different shirt.
That has a different vibe!
Should I follow what Sung Woo taught me?
(Shall I dress like how my fashion guru taught me?)
It's a style that allows me to mingle with the locals.
This looks nice.
All right.
A mix-and-match style.
Can I try this on?
It looks like it took him only two minutes to choose.
- I picked them really fast. - Right?
(Going to the fitting room after picking clothes without hesitating)
(Excited)
(He transformed into a city-style man.)
He keeps wearing sleeveless shirts because of you.
(Watching intently)
(I look kind of cool.)
(Spreading)
- It looks nice. - Well, it's...
- It's not bad. - Right?
It's not bad.
- It's not nice, either. - Right.
- But it's neat. - Yes, it's neat.
- He looks like a successful man. - CODE KUNST approved of it.
(Thinking)
The shirt...
(Changing the shirt)
Goodness.
(Sighing)
(This isn't right.)
I picked a shirt that would be on display...
in the shop that CODE KUNST took me to.
(Super proud)
- That looks airier, though. - Right?
- The shirt I wore earlier... - It looked hot.
- You taught me this. - Was it heavy?
You said a shirt that's either too big...
or too small looks cool.
But that shirt wasn't either big or small.
You can only make that decision after taking lesson two.
(The student took it too far after taking only lesson 1.)
- Don't decide by yourself. - He only took lesson one.
- You can't decide yet. - He hasn't taken the next lesson.
Don't decide on your own.
- That's right. - Okay.
Please give me a little discount.
(He skillfully pays for it.)
Oh, right. The backpack doesn't suit my style now.
I failed to take it into consideration.
(He goes outside after transforming into a city man.)
(Striding with confidence)
A taxi.
Hi.
(City man Ji Hyeon hurriedly gets on the taxi.)
Gosh, it was good to be back.
(He heads somewhere, putting aside the joy of being back.)
It's incredible.
The shirt and the vibe suit each other well.
Gosh, the night view of Shanghai.
It's breathtaking.
(Evening has fallen before he realized it.)
(He gets out somewhere.)
Is he meeting someone now?
I can't predict who he is going to meet at all.
- I know. Who is it? - I know. Who is it?
(Walking straight on)
(Ji Hyeon walks into a building.)
- Hello. - Hello.
The place looks fancy.
Are you visiting the restaurant?
Yes.
- The elevator will come soon. - Thank you.
- It must need reservations. - Thank you.
(He gets in the elevator while getting escorted.)
It looks like he's going somewhere really fancy.
- I was even escorted too. - Right.
Gosh, it smells nice.
- Gosh. What is this? - Gosh.
It's so nice.
It looks like a really fancy restaurant.
(Amazed)
- Gosh! - It's no joke, right?
- Gosh. - It's amazing.
(Eyes going wide)
(A high-end restaurant with a refined ambiance)
- Gosh, the view! - Look at the view.
They're gold-trimmed. It must be an expensive restaurant.
Ji Hyeon spent a lot of money there.
It's the representative night view of Shanghai.
(The night view of the Oriental Pearl Tower is visible at a glance.)
For the person I'm meeting today,
I reserved a high-end restaurant...
with a nice view.
I've made it.
I've made it. That's why I reserved a restaurant like that.
Otherwise, I couldn't go there.
He's made it.
I've made it.
(I can't believe I came to a place with a Shanghai night view.)
- The night view is really nice. - It really is.
I'd never been to a restaurant that nice either.
(What is this?)
It's gold-trimmed.
(There are many fascinating things here.)
Why are there two pairs of chopsticks and spoons?
They give you two pairs of chopsticks?
One's for grabbing food, and the other one is for eating.
They're shared chopsticks.
I didn't know that.
That's how they use chopsticks in Chinese cuisine.
(He begins exploring in earnest.)
(Nodding)
(Checking out thoroughly)
(Amazed)
Goodness.
Gosh, what is this?
It really is a fancy restaurant.
Yes, it really was.
I'd never been to such a fancy restaurant.
Gosh, they customized these into perfect sizes.
My goodness.
It's about time they got here.
(Knocking)
They're here.
- Oh, you're here. - Gosh, it's a celeb.
- "Oh, you're here?" - "Oh, you're here?"
Is it a friend?
(Gosh, it's a celeb.)
- Who is it? - You're here.
He's Yoon Young Pyo,
my classmate from the Chinese Language Department...
at Honam University. We entered college in 2014.
If it had been just me,
I'd have never gone to a restaurant like that.
But my friend...
has become a teacher now.
And he's preparing to get a doctoral degree.
So I went there to celebrate it.
My friend lives in China, and he works there.
(He visited his friend to root for him in person.)
You look so much better.
That's why he can speak...
- in a charming dialect. - He speaks in dialect right away.
I got to visit a place like this thanks to you. It's neat.
It's so nice.
- "It's neat." - "It's neat."
We were really close when we were in college.
I slept over at his place all the time.
There are friends like that.
(They order their food first.)
- What do they have? - Order whatever you want to eat.
- What do you want to eat? - Is there anything you can't eat?
I can eat anything. What's this? Let's have this.
Is it grilled meat?
It's pan-fried.
- Pan-fried? - What?
- What does that mean? - It's pan-fried.
(It means it's pan-fried.)
What seafood dishes do you have?
Is there a menu you'd like to recommend to us?
Is this the only spicy dish you have?
(Young Pyo orders in fluent Chinese.)
You really sound like a teacher now.
- Come on! - He really does.
You don't hesitate at all.
- I don't teach carelessly. - I know.
"Carelessly."
- "Carelessly." - "I don't teach carelessly."
Order a lot. Order everything you want to eat.
Why don't you have a glass of wine?
- Wine. - Really? Then...
Let's have this.
- Gosh, you're a successful friend. - This will be fine.
You say that a lot to the friends you feel grateful to...
- after making a lot of money. - Right.
- "Order everything you want." - That's right.
You'd say things like, "Tell me whatever you want to get."
(Staring)
Gosh, you're going to get a doctoral degree?
I can't believe it either.
(Embarrassed)
(Look how much we've grown.)
What do you teach, then?
It's something like this.
You teach? What do you know?
- I pretend to know. - Exactly. What do you teach?
- They're true friends. - You teach in Korean?
A conversation between true friends.
I teach Korean, basically.
Don't you need to speak in standard Korean to teach Korean?
I speak like this because I'm with you.
I'm really good at standard Korean.
- Seriously. - That's dirty.
- "That's dirty." - Totally dirty.
Seriously. I'm really good at standard Korean.
(Firm)
I can't be like this to the Chinese students.
"Gosh, what shall we learn today?"
(That's true.)
You're amazing.
You became a teacher in China.
- And one became a singer. - I still can't believe it.
- It feels like a dream. - And one became a teacher.
I am amazing too.
You're friends who remember...
- each other's lousy sides. - Yes.
It must feel weird to see one another's success.
- It must feel weird. - Right.
That's right.
By the way, where did you buy your clothes?
Yes.
Did someone style you?
No, I did it myself.
- Goodness, you learned? - I chose them myself.
- I did. - From who?
- Do you know who CODE KUNST is? - You look nice.
- "Do you know who CODE KUNST is?" - "Do you know who CODE KUNST is?"
(Smiling)
Since he's my fashion guru.
Of course.
- He dresses well. - That's right.
You know CODE KUNST dresses well too?
Of course.
If I look at you like this,
you look like...
- Seo In Guk a little. - What is it?
(Me?)
(Smiling from ear to ear)
You're so happy about it.
Seeing you smiling like that,
you look a bit...
You look a bit foolish.
(You look a bit foolish.)
- You're giving off that vibe. - Is that so?
- You two look really close. - Right.
You care about each other too.
- And you offend each other a bit. - Right.
(The dishes are served 1 by 1 while they catch up.)
- Isn't it delicious? - Yes.
(Pouring)
(Impressed)
- She poured it. - What is that?
- Have you ever seen that? - What is that?
It's no joke.
- It's a decanter. - The flavor changes.
- How can it be possible? - As it meets oxygen.
Oh, then the flavor becomes richer?
Aerating.
Gosh, it's to die for.
It's to die for.
My gosh. I didn't know the glass would be this big.
- My goodness. - I know.
- So? Shall we clink our glasses? - It's as big as my face.
- We should clink, right? - It's needless to say.
Of course, we should clink our glasses.
My gosh. The sound is amazing too.
It's amazing, isn't it?
- I know. - Seriously.
Gosh, Ji Hyeon, you're so cool. You became successful...
and had wine in Shanghai.
With a background like that.
I've made it.
(Knocking)
- Someone else is here. - What?
What's that? What did you order?
Oh, it must be their food.
- It's incredible. - Gosh.
- What is that? - Oh, my.
Oh, my.
- It's huge. - I know.
- It's lobster. That's right. - The food...
- It's no joke. - It's lobster.
It's stir-fried lobster.
Gosh, look at all this meat.
It's amazing.
- It's the steak we ordered earlier. - Is it steak?
It's a must to order a steak and a lobster.
That's right.
When you treat a meal for your friend after becoming successful.
(What do you think?)
- It's huge. - I know.
Do you think they cooked the head as well?
Or do you think it's just for decoration?
- It's for decoration. - Right?
It's for decoration.
- Right? - It looks like they reuse this.
I think they use it for decoration.
But the roe... Look. It's huge.
- That's for decoration. - They just cooked it.
- They just cooked it. - "They just cooked it."
That's right. They just...
- cooked the alive one. - Yes.
- They must've cooked it. - It's real.
- Gosh, there's meat in here too. - That's right.
- See inside here. - It was freshly caught.
They scraped the meat out of it for the dish.
My goodness.
We should try a bite...
- since it's served, right? - Yes, we should.
Right? Let's have the big piece.
This is amazing.
- Look how plump it is. - It must be delicious.
My goodness.
(Gulping)
(Taking a bite)
(Impressed)
(Amazed)
Hey, it's bouncy.
You're right.
- Shall we cut it? - Yes, we shall.
My goodness.
It's different.
(Cutting)
It's somewhat different.
- He's cutting it. - It feels different.
It's no joke.
The marbling is no joke.
(Impressed)
- Is it so good? - It's good, right?
It's delicious.
(It's delicious.)
They look like kids who are quickly eating food...
before the rich owner of the house comes back home.
"Hurry up and eat! We don't have much time."
- "They're coming!" - They're so cute.
- Have a drink. - Gosh, this is nice.
I was really happy because my friend seemed happy.
I know.
That's how it was.
I got you something.
- What is it? - What did you get?
I got you this.
Don't make me excited.
For real?
Here.
I hope you'll get your doctoral degree.
(A gift Ji Hyeon got him to root for his success in doctoral degree)
I didn't get you anything.
For real, this is...
- What is it? - What is it?
- What is it? - What is that?
(Curious)
My gosh.
- Honestly... - Yes.
- I looked forward to it a little. - I didn't write anything.
- Gosh. - A letter between two men?
You don't write letters to your true friend.
- I know. - It'll give me goosebumps.
That's right.
- I thought I'd see something. - You think I'm crazy?
(You think I'm crazy?)
- That's real. - It's so real.
- It is real. - "You think I'm crazy?"
He meant it.
- A fountain pen. - Right.
It's not a fountain pen.
- It's a ballpoint pen. - A ballpoint pen?
I was going to get you a fountain pen.
Fountain pens are inconvenient.
- You have to keep filling the ink. - You can never use it.
I thought you wouldn't use a fountain pen.
You need to keep refilling ink.
Y. P. Yoon.
I engraved your name too. Isn't it cool?
Gosh, thank you so much.
(Pleased)
I'll make sure to use this.
After writing the thesis for my doctoral degree,
I'll use this to sign it.
I'll let my name show.
Before I get the degree...
Even I feel moved. I feel proud for him.
I'll show the side that has my name.
- All right. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Make sure to get the doctoral degree.
Seriously.
Come again next time. I'm serious. I'm not joking.
- Goodness. - Thanks for coming.
- I'll treat you to a meal. - Get the doctoral degree, okay?
I really will.
The day I spent in Shanghai...
(The day I spent in Shanghai...)
I had a lot of mixed feelings.
If my past self from 20 years ago...
appeared before me today,
I think...
I'd have been emotional.
"What would've happened if I hadn't gone to China?"
I had such thoughts.
"What if my parents' businesses had done well?"
But I became a singer...
because they went bankrupt.
You never know what life has in store.
So it's okay.
It's just part of my memory.
Looking back, the bad things that happened to us...
became memories now.
- It's a good memory. - He grew up to be amazing.
(Everything that's gone by becomes a cherished memory.)
You should be the World Star.
No, that's too much.
(Shanghai Carries the Memories)
(Next story)
(Hye Young kept her pace and was relaxed.)
(A day she starts in her own style)
(Shall I go out since I'm done studying?)
(Who did Hye Young go out to see?)
(Actor Ko Kyoung Pyo)
(They were an older woman, younger man couple...)
(in "Reply 1988.")
(In real life, they're friends who went to the same college.)
(Film Department, Konkuk University, entered in 2010)
(Film Department, Konkuk University, entered in 2009)
(Their friendship has been lasted for 16 years.)
(When my parents came to my house,)
(you came out of it instead of me.)
(Oh, right. That happened.)
(There's no need for us to save face with each other.)
(I'm happy to have a friend...)
(whom I can enjoy summer with.)
(They bicker nonstop.)
(He hates it.)
(Every day is so precious during summer.)
(Violet Summer)
I'm in a hurry.
(Laughing)
(The Chunks have gathered.)
(For the hungry Chunks,)
(Hwan prepared a full Kumakase.)
(The first destination...)
(is Mexico.)
(Taking big bites instead of putting on a seatbelt)
(The next destination is the rooftop.)
(A chunk of Korean beef for the Chunks)
(Chunks, what do you think of this flavor?)
(Sailing safely on the charcoal)
(Taking a bite)
(It's the most delicious thing I've had this year.)
(Thrilled)
Let's grill a few.
(You're grilling marinated crabs?)
(A special menu for Kumakase)
(Entering the new world of flavors)
(Kumakase isn't over yet.)
(Something big must be coming.)
(The marvelous real deal is entering.)
(What did the Chunks see?)
(Splashing into the World of Gourmet Food)